[主讲老师 - @亚嵌李明老师, AKAEDU] 好，我们在当前目录下先新建一个文件夹,
取名叫 myNCCL，代表的是我们自己要写的所有的C程序。
接下来我们要打开一个Lesson-1.c
You're going to learn some of the core ideas in computer science.
You're going to learn to program in a language called Python,
and you're going to build a search engine that by the end of 7 weeks
will have all the main components of a search engine like Google in it.
Learning about computing is really one of the most powerful things you can do.
Computers are these amazing machines that can be programmed to do anything.
And once you learn a little bit about programming, you can sort of start to envision
the power that you have, the things that you can build with computers.
One of the great things about computing is that you don't really need a lot of resources
to build something that can change the world.
If you learn a little bit, if you have a creative idea,
you can build something, you can deploy your application to millions of people
on the Internet, and it doesn't really take a lot of resources to do that.
It just takes a little creativity and a little bit of knowledge.
So David, this is really exciting. I'm looking forward to seeing your class.
I'll be making occasional appearances, but I have my own class to teach.
But David will teach this wonderful class, and I think we should just dive in.
Great! Well, let's get started.